4ip.me 2016-11-25

# Privacy

## Terms of Service

### Acceptance of Terms

By using 4ip.me (“”) you agree that you are over 18 years of age and have the ability to enter into a binding agreement. Any access to or use of 4ip.me constitutes acceptance of the following Terms of Service (“TOS”).

4ip.me offers a variety of services and products that may or may not incur fees on your part. Use of any services or products, including both products and services that do require a fee, and those that do not require a fee, constitutes acceptance of and agreement to this TOS.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ANY PROVISION IN THE FOLLOWING TOS OR IF ANY SECTION OF THE TOS IS BREACHED BY YOU; YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO, AND SHALL NOT USE OR CONTINUE TO USE, OUR SERVICES.

Please contact us if you have any questions about any provision in this agreement.

### Responsibilities and Regulations

Use of our services requires that you agree to uphold the following responsibilities and abide by the following regulations. Failure to do so in any constitutes immediate breach of this TOS.

You may not use our site to engage in any behavior that violates any local law or any law or regulation that is applicable to the venue created in this agreement. This prohibition includes, but is in no way limited to, use of our products or services in any way associated with activities that:

(a) involve sending emails that: (i) are not CAN-SPAM complaint or (ii) are unsolicited by the receiver (iii) or involve the marketing of products or services that violate any applicable law or regulation to 4ip.me or you including but not limited to: pharmaceutical products, firearms, narcotics, products or services that violate another parties trademark, products or services that violate another parties copyright or (iv) collect and/or harvest third party information in a deceptive or illegal manner or (v) encourage or distribute the use of any fraudulent business practices.

(b) attack, harass, threaten, defame, or otherwise infringe on the legal rights of any other individual or entity including but not limited to protection afforded to them via applicable criminal or privacy regulations.

(c) violate or would cause 4ip.me to violate any law, regulation or ethical standard. 4ip.me reserves the right to determine and establish what constitutes both what qualifies as a violation or ethical standard in our sole discretion at any time.

You agree that you will not sell, copy, publish or otherwise distribute any of our products or services in any way. You agree that none of the products or services obtained throught 4ip.me will be used in a manner that either directly or indirectly competes with or is similar to the business model used by 4ip.me.

### Our disclosure of and how we use your information

Your personal contact information will be handled in accordance with the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy, which is incorporated in its entirety into this Agreement,

Your personal information obtained by either your submission or our collection may be used in the following ways:

(a) For verification and/or clarification of orders; or

(b) For management of your services; or

(c) To let you know about the promotion of products and services that might be of interest to you as made available directly from 4ip.me and from trusted third parties.

Furthermore, we may provide information that we retain to private or public third parties including but not limited to:

(a) For inspection by law enforcement officials; or

(b) In response to criminal or civil subpoenas and court orders, or any other legal obligation;or

(c) In connection with the sale of all or a portion of our assets; or

(d)For compliance with any rule, regulation or policy of ICANN or any governmental entity; or

(e)For purposes of inspection and any other purposes as may be required or permitted by applicable laws.

We will take reasonable precautions to protect personal contact information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

### Waiver

If we fail to require your performance of a provision of this Agreement, it will not be considered a waiver of our right to require such performance at any later time. Our waiver of a breach of any provision of this Agreement will not be considered a waiver of the provision itself, nor a waiver of that breach or any future breach.

### Web browser cookies 

4ip.me use cookies to provide the best experience of the website.   
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

### Non-personal identification information 

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to 4ip.me and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://google.com/privacy_ads.html

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Changes to this privacy policy

4ip.me has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

* * *
